Thank you, Pierre-Seung-Tee's cross.
Thank you.
Thank you, Robert.
Dr. Kulu-Pu,
Dr. Kulu,
Congratulations to the 5th,
The 9th and 7th of America.
And to the Republic of which stands,
Lineation,
a new law,
New University,
and,
Mr. Sura,
thanks for the invitation.
I am proud of the public and
put on special personal services
and the audits that were
to address the authority
on any of the agenda items.
I don't know if five is concerned, Jim, the staff is recommending item six to ten for the
consent agenda.
There are no questions on either of them, so you have a motion and a second.
Second.
We'll call please.
Johnson.
Weston.
Forester.
Five.
Lewis.
High.
Thank you.
I don't know.
Eleven.
Electrical capital improvement.
Budget amendment to include increasing.
Electrical department by two FTEs.
Tyler.
Good.
I know this is not the first time we've talked about this, but we're fresh our memory.
Please.
So if you remember back in the last year, we had Will the Empire in Trocambam, Dan Jackson,
and do the presentation on the electric rating, as part of that injury, City prepare, we
staffed and prepared a list of capital improvements in capital outlay items and also personnel.
And we talked about two additional personnel for maintenance of the system.
So tonight we're coming to you for approval for the two additional personnel and also for three
capital outlay items, a service truck, a digger truck, and also a UTV, which there's
some pictures of different things we want to do with them.
And there's a slide with the actual price of each of them, or that anticipated price.
So this particular agenda item is just the FTEs later on, we'll be addressing the capital
and the FTEs tonight, so we would like to do it amendment for the two to budget.
We're going to have to use this part of the number of people, so we can look at it.
We've had it in 1996, 185 full-time, and then we have 33 part-time, and that's a ratio of 3 to 1.
So right now we have 1096 full-time.
So if we add it to full ton of boys, that would take us to 188.
So, so B.C. on the slide at three of the breakdown of the two elements with their salary and benefits.
And you sort of strike the digger truck in the UTV, which for the happy year of the 153,000 to our 50 dollars,
and currently we are up to $175,000, based on the increase.
with doing this, we would have a remaining revenue on 21,000.
Any questions all this was in the budget?
I just, the agenda item confused me a little bit,
but it's in the VA that the equipment is part of this agenda item,
which is not spelled out specifically in the language of the agenda item.
Are you comfortable with that, man?
OK.
What, what, what do you TV be looking to need?
Just one, I mean, you see a area that out of the display that our feeder lines down.
We just didn't get a UTV, just to build a go down these areas in the spray.
If you didn't go back to the slide, they've been shown in the areas that we've...
So, for example, if you go out at one of these seconds,
you see the trees that were getting to the power lines causing outages to end up short customers,
we went in there, their track out, and...
That was, that was the city doing that?
Yes.
How across the rubber tracks on the left side, okay?
So, we're trying to have that service front of a store of customers up here there.
So, we've been on the other area, I mean, this is there, that's a bit touched on a long time.
So, once we go in there and clean it up, we would like to go in there with this UTV,
it's spray to keep the trees from going back in there and just be there.
So, that's how we fish out, so we'll keep it fish out.
So, Vicky's sitting on the one and what's a UTV?
I mean, I know what it is, but she was wondering, so...
I mean, I'm thinking of something that's sprays things, and what's the people looking for?
I'm wondering myself.
Okay, so it is, if you've seen, like, there's different brands, but there's a cap, you said it,
and then I have a bed on the back, which is the bed is where you put your spray tank, or whatever you want to use.
So, like, G-O-D-A, they have a spray tank in the back of there, so they can just drive along the easement,
just spray to kill the trees, keep the...
So, it's a UTV V-Hick, all the way to the UTV, put a spray on the end.
Yes, sir.
There's all different brands, there's the layers, there's new, there's come to the end.
Right.
Okay.
Any other questions?
The additional truck that we're going to be getting, we're not taking the old one out.
Yes, sir.
It's pretty good.
Both of those are on a plus, the additional one they've had, but we're out on the other side of
my second last week with two deers, but in new pulses, part of the system maintenance, we're
trying to do this year, so...
I came to get a bit of this, it brings up to a hundred and ninety-eight, it's better than it's.
What's our limit, sir?
I'm sorry, because that's not just one of the three of just...
Yes?
I mean, if we had this, it's going to have to make sure that you're not going to be bothered.
Okay.
I just want to share what our ordinance said, if that's long, I guess it has been a little bit
of time, but I think we're going to have to be able to have a proof of that.
Okay.
And all three of these pieces of equipment are new, right?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
And so just to follow up on the old's point, by virtue of improving this, what are our raising the FTEs,
you're going to bring another item before.
Or is this in fact raising that level?
Well, I think we're giving you a approval of this point
and that we've got to make sure that we have
the kind of our group level of the point that we're going to want.
So, Kim, can you come back up with that?
So, the evidence is that what was published in the budget
cannot only be increased in a team that was by the council.
So, my understanding has been correct.
And if I'm wrong, I mean, it's that way you approving this,
then that will increase our number to the 1.98.
And that is covering the ordinance.
It just says, it can't just be randomly increased
without council.
So, it's not like it's 1.95 and we have to do this and then
vote to improve it to 1.97.
We approve this.
That raises that level.
That's part of it.
And I went back and wanted the budget before the meeting to make sure
that is the right number.
So, I mean, we read the reports.
If you approve this, we'll be fine to be able to work the two of us.
And with these two employees, Kim, they're going to be coming in
at the bottom of their band and grade and they're going to work their way through
just like any normal person being hired in a new position.
So, I will say yes.
The only exception to that would be that they would make an exception.
Let's say we have alignment that maybe had 20 years of experience.
The only exception can be made from the bottom is that we have somebody
and then only somewhere between the bottom to the mid.
Usually, that's not an almost situation.
Usually, people come in at the bottom of the band.
What?
Association's wife is going to have a partnership, but it's really precious.
And I think we've talked about trying to kind of grow.
In the past, we've hired a lot of money and we're trying to talk about
growing from within and trying to growing our own.
That's one of the reasons that we've started doing this in the internship for Rams.
The last couple years, thinking it will have some good.
Yes.
People come out of that.
But that's what I want to do.
The technical school and then came to us as a second year.
And when you develop the grades and bands for this position a year or two ago,
you took into account the current market rates.
So, we should be competitive at entry level.
And we're just now meeting this week on the reshaw of this hour study.
But I can tell you from the information that we have there.
Of course not.
There's no problem.
I'm not.
All right.
Not because there's just something you're wanting to feel right away.
Yes, let's get the process started this first.
Yeah, every time.
Everything.
With this, so you're just what you're saying is with the current.
I'm going to go back to my slide here.
Your numbers are okay because your revenues are up and you project them to stay out.
And the revenues for the line, that's actually a journey of it.
So if we hire a second year, then we can say we'll let you go.
It all goes back because back to that meeting, I remember we talked about transfers and I'm
always not on transfers and I, it's so easy to understand how transfers work, but it's
you take from one for so much and then they don't have anything, so I feel good that
our, this number will be, we want to make sure that the revenues coming in will be
covered.
Okay.
I just don't have to say any sort of, right, and I just, that's what I don't want to get into,
transfer this, transfer this out of the utilities department that we've went and asked
and we're going to do a bond on and now we're, so I just want to make sure we're going in
the right direction.
So we can lay this kind of view itself.
And the revenue will continue to come in to pay the remaining years to go down the line to pay
for the salary and the least fees of all this equipment.
Okay.
And the source of the increased revenues is the rating increase that we have proved based
on the world and study.
Sorry.
But I remember one of the reasons we called off is we didn't rate increase, so we had to be asked
to go to the bottom, so even with the rate increase, we didn't have the revenue for what's
gone.
But now we're kind of, we're to the level of whether we're starting to see the revenue coming.
For you, if you don't want that, make sure that we have the revenue gone.
Were you a fully staff career right now?
We have six right now.
Is that, were you need to pay?
I don't think so.
I mean, the full higher in these two, are you?
You are really low.
We are very low.
I mean, we're going to make a bunch of questions.
What do you want six?
And you have six.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
And this will now we're looking at authorized AA.
So for the proof is, we're approving the, the, the two addition.
The two addition left to ease is when we need further action by the council required for
that to happen for that limit to increase, so to speak, and also the three pieces of equipment.
Do we have a motion?
I'll make a motion.
And a second?
A second.
Roll call, please.
Four, sir.
All right.
Lewis, I, Weston, Johnson.
Show.
Bye.
Thank you.
Any new business?
Any other business?
Staff report during your pocket?
Any community announcements?
Do we have a motion to join?
Motion.
Okay.
Roll call.
Four, sir.